{
  "title": "Mean, Median, Modes Checkin",
  "questions": [
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>mean</b> of the dataset: 17, 23, 25, 23, 22"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "22"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>mean</b> of the dataset: 11, 3, 4, 5, 7"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "6"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>mean</b> of the dataset: 11, 3, 4, 7"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "6.25"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>mean</b> of the dataset: 5, 7, 11, 11, 7, 7"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "8"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>mean</b> of the dataset: 2, 3, 5, 4, 3, 7, 4"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "4"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>median</b> of the dataset: 17, 23, 25, 23, 22"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "23"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>median</b> of the dataset: 11, 3, 4, 5, 7"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "5"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>median</b> of the dataset: 11, 3, 4, 7"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "5.5"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>median</b> of the dataset: 5, 7, 11, 11, 7, 7"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "7"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>median</b> of the dataset: 2, 3, 5, 4, 3, 7, 4"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "4"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>mode(s)</b> of the dataset: 17, 23, 25, 23, 22\n\n If there is no mode, write: none\n\n If there is more than one mode, separate the numbers with commas, for example by writing: 5,7"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "23"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>mode(s)</b> of the dataset: 11, 3, 4, 5, 7\n\n If there is no mode, write: none\n\n If there is more than one mode, separate the numbers with commas, for example by writing: 5,7"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "none"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>mode(s)</b> of the dataset: 11, 3, 4, 7 \n\n If there is no mode, write: none\n\n If there is more than one mode, separate the numbers with commas, for example by writing: 5,7"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "none"
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>mode(s)</b> of the dataset: 5, 7, 11, 11, 7, 7\n\n If there is no mode, write: none\n\n If there is more than one mode, separate the numbers with commas, for example by writing: 5,7"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "7"
      }
    }, 
    {
      "type": "ShortAnswer",
      "prompt": {
        "prompt": "Find the <b>mode(s)</b> of the dataset: 2, 3, 5, 4, 3, 7, 4\n\n If there is no mode, write: none\n\n If there is more than one mode, separate the numbers with commas, for example by writing: 5,7"
      },
      "answer": {
        "answer": "3, 4"
      }
    }
  ]
}